♪ In the not too distant future
♪ Next Sunday, AD
♪ There was a guy named Joel
♪ Not too different
from you or me
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place
♪ But his bosses didn't like 'im
♪ So they shot him into space
(rocket launching)
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst we can find
♪ La la la
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all
♪ And we'll monitor his mind
♪ La la la
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control
♪ Where the movies begin or end
♪ La la la
♪ Because he used
those special parts
♪ To make his robot friends
♪ Robot roll call
♪ Cambot
♪ Gypsy
♪ Tom Servo
♪ Crow
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♪ And other science facts
♪ La la la
♪ Then repeat to yourself
♪ It's just a show
♪ I should really just relax
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000
(metal sliding and clanging)
Hi, welcome to the
Satellite of Love.
My name's Joel,
and I've fashioned
my two robot friends,
Tom and Crow,
into an at-home
shooting gallery.
It does get boring up here.
Stop talking and
start chalking.
(gun firing, bullet pinging)
As you can probably tell
from the opening the Mads made,
I'm marooned up here in space,
without much chance of
ever really getting home.
Something is wrong on Saturn 3
(gun firing, bullet pinging)
Anyway, they
monitor our responses
to watching really bad movies,
and then they sell the
results to cable TV.
Five seconds to
commercial sign.
Say, partner, that's some
mighty fancy shootin'.
(gun firing, bullet pinging)
Thank you.
Commercial sign in five
four, three, two.
Commercial sign now.
We'll be right back.
(gun firing repeatedly,
bullets pinging)
(MST3K theme music)
Hey everybody, look,
I changed the robots to
Apple Dumpling Gang mode.
Draw, Tim Conway!
Uh, er, Jeepers!
Sorry about getting that
ketchup on your
scarf, Mr. Black Bart.
Can I call you Bart?
Is that okay with you?
Uh, gee, I'll get some soda
water and clean that right up.
(gun firing, bullet pinging)
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Now, your turn, Don Knotts.
I'll have you know,
these hands have to be
registered as lethal weapons
with the Mount Pilot
police department.
And when in Los Angeles,
visit Universal Studios.
(gun firing, bullet pinging)
Oh, you guys, wake up!
The Mads are calling.
Come on, get up!
Hi!
Hello, evil over,
under, over lords.
Oh, shut your
mouth, Pollyanna Prod,
and show us your
invention exchange.
And don't dawdle, Amaryllis.
Do you mean me?
No, him, Beefaroni.
Well, sirs, today's
invention exchange
is based on the old premise
of this age-old
gag, the bang gun.
It's not that great.
Not really that much fun.
So, I took that premise, and
based it on this new bang Uzi.
See, you can point it
directly at someone,
and if you do it right.
Real arcade action!
Gimme two!
- Well?
- Kaboom.
Ah, very funny.
We can do better than that.
In fact, we've come up
with this harpoon gun
with appropriate noise.
Start running, Frank.
Oh, I hate this one!
Shh-toonk (vibrating sound).
Funny, huh? (exhales)
Well, hey, sirs.
Here's a knife adapted
to the same purpose.
Shhhhlink?
Well, ball's in your court.
Ball's in our court?
I'll show you balls.
Frank has got some nun-chucks
using the same tired premise.
Hi-kee-ba!
In-sa-no-bock.
Well, here's a
stick o'dynamite.
Just light the fuse.
Oh, I can't hold my ears.
And...
Ka-chow!
Ka-chow? Ka-chow?
What, is Don Martin
working with you guys now?
Frank, get the plunger ready.
Well, your experiment
this week, Joel,
is a TV movie called
Stranded in Space.
It's a real stinker.
And, I'm sorry.
But, if I don't do
it, someone else will.
Finish him off, Frank.
Boingee-banga-kabonga?
(all exclaiming)
(metal sliding and clanging)
Now, was that
bingo-bango-kabongo?
That was weird.
Boingo-bango-ka. Oh.
Oh, make it stop!
It's being seen
through the eyes
of Yule Brenner
in Westworld here.
You know, already
this movie's like
goin' to the dentist.
(Tom chuckling)
Yeah.
All right, your order is $5.25.
Please drive forward to the
first window, thank you.
Now, you know,
I don't think we should get
wrapped up in these credits.
I'm sure they have nothing
to do with the movie.
Hmm, Shrinky Dinks!
Wait a minute.
Oh, wait.
I think I see Charles
Foster Kane's sled in there.
In Xanadu.
Time to start thinking
about me, Steve Franken.
Tim Conway, Dorf in Space?
Oh, Tim O'Connnor.
Sorry.
Woop!
Oh, damn roller-blades!
I can't stop it, I
don't know how it works.
Goodbye, folks!
Goodbye!
Hmmm. Uh-oh.
Oh, that's bad luck
- Three in a transporter?
- Yeah.
Mmm-huh.
Now, see,
what did that have
to do with the movie?
Nothing.
You know, I just had
the craziest dream.
And you were there.
And you, Tim.
That one doesn't work anymore.
Everything checks out okay.
And so do I.
Now, let's see if we
can strand this baby.
Houston, this is Patriot.
Reading you loud
and clear, Neil.
Steve's checked and
rechecked the transponder.
We can't find anything
wrong with it on this end.
Roger.
Looks like you'll
have to continue
performing your correction burns
using your on-board computer.
And using those sideburns
we set ya up with.
Roger.
At least our computer seems
to be functioning okay.
Oh, those are
the lotto numbers.
In case we can't locate
the problem down here,
you should be close
enough in about seven days
for us to skin paint
you on our radar.
- Skin paint?
- Roger.
Well, I'll try anything once.
After all this
time in deep space,
I guess we can
wait another week.
Good one.
Everything else
all right up there?
Aside from the fact we're
not a hundred percent sure
we're on the right trajectory,
everything's great.
And, we ran outta
oxygen two days ago.
We'll keep in touch.
We'll be here.
So, whose turn was it?
Hey, it's I Dream of Jeannie.
Oh!
Hey, was that us?
I never thought I'd consider
26,000 miles-an-hour slow.
Until I popped a Dexatrim.
You get the feeling Mike's
a little anxious to get home?
Well, a new bride
will do that to you.
Especially when you
haven't had a chance
to take her on a honeymoon.
Don't worry, I'll make
up for it when I get back.
And how!
He's right, folks.
Watch out for that one.
Whoa.
What's on the menu, Junior?
There's a real pretty sight.
- Where that transponder bailed.
- It's a Universal picture.
I wasn't really
sure I'd see it again.
That makes two of us.
Uh, that's three, Steve.
Might carve out a
nice, thick, juicy--
(explosion)
Seizure! Ah!
Set up our
communications line.
Was that it the food tube?
Try and get 'em reset,
Steve. (alarm blares)
I'll see if we still have
voice to Mission Control.
Houston, this is
Patriot, do you read me?
Must be time for class.
Houston, this is patriot!
Yeah, it's a honeymoon, man.
Woo!
(radio breaking up)
(Tom chuckling)
We're havin' Ray
Bolger practice!
We're doing acting improv.
We're bacon!
Bacon.
Bacon?
Meanwhile, on Trapper John.
Hey, maybe we'll
see Chad Everett.
Your telegrams.
Uh, thanks for
the horse, Mary Lou.
It's Consuela.
Directing her in there?
Hi.
Fred MacMurray wants
his slippers back.
More telegrams.
You think they'd be
out of paper by now.
I wish you had toilet
paper in this room.
Can I get you anything?
How 'bout a room with a view?
Or a pretty woman?
I'm afraid there
are no windows
in this wing of the hospital.
Sunlight interferes with
post-radiation studies.
Besides, you'll be well
enough to leave here soon.
Straight scoop?
Double dip?
(laughing nervously)
In the meanwhile,
there're all these
beautiful flowers.
They keep coming in
by the truckload.
They're all poppies,
heh-heh-heh-heh.
My God, you're ugly.
Well, how's our
number one patient?
Uh, he just went
number two, Doctor.
Can't say I blame him.
How do you feel?
- You tell me.
- You're hot.
You're making
excellent progress.
Good, then I can
get outta here soon.
Soon?
It's not as though we're
a prison, you know.
What would you
call it, Dr. Revere?
Call me Paul.
The two weeks I've been here,
I haven't been allowed
outside this room.
I can't have visitors,
use the telephone,
or read a newspaper.
I've been cut off from
the outside world,
and you tell me it's
not like I'm in prison.
You've been through
a terrible experience.
But I'm still in one piece!
I can get around.
I know, physically,
you're in better condition
than we could've hoped, but.
But, what?
Emotionally.
You'll always
be a little girl.
What about emotionally?
It just takes time.
You've been a member
of the space program
long enough to understand that.
I don't know what
I understand anymore.
All I know is,
I haven't seen one familiar
face since I got back,
and you're as much a
stranger to me as anyone.
(Dr. Revere chuckling)
That's pretty good!
There are many people
in this end of the program
you've never come
in contact with.
What about our flight surgeon?
Uh, we had to shoot 'im.
He had a broken leg.
Dr. Bellman is dead, Neil.
He died of a heart attack
while you were still in space.
We didn't wanna
disturb you with it.
I'm sorry.
Jell-O?
Look, I give you my word
that it won't be
long before you'll
be reunited with
the outside world,
and with your
family and friends.
- You know, all that crap.
- We need you back in space.
You're much too valuable
to be stuck in here.
In the meantime,
reports concerning your health
- are being let out.
- And so is your gown.
You know there are
people all over the world
concerned about your well-being?
I told you, didn't I?
The president himself
insisted upon being
the first one to speak
to you on the telephone?
What, so all of a
sudden he's a cable show?
And keep him informed.
(suspenseful music)
Kinda fuzzy.
Steve Austin! (gasps)
Sort of.
Okay, we're ready to
lay in the background
vocals now.
(speaking in foreign language)
- I'm sorry.
- Bless you.
You don't speak
Russian, Doctor?
No.
I never had time to
learn another language.
Nice try, astro-spy.
I smell a rat,
a big Commie rat.
Can I have some
borscht, Dr. Stalin?
You find these have
been helping you relax?
Yeah, but I haven't
been sleeping well lately.
Now, uh, now the arm.
Keep having these
strange dreams.
About the mission?
About everything that's
ever happened to me.
It's like I'm reliving my
life over again in my sleep.
Even the smallest details.
Only Cameron Mitchell's there.
And, I've got the feeling
I've been talking
in my sleep, too.
And wetting.
Sorry.
Well, our nurses are
trained to be discreet.
Say, I think I'll
test that theory.
I think I told you that
the fact that you survived,
and your fellow
astronauts perished,
that makes it all the
more traumatic for ya.
But these nightmares,
they'll pass.
So will your suspicions,
and your fears.
And your kidney stones.
You're getting
better, colonel.
Just takes time.
The check's in
the mail. (chuckles)
Oh, say, I've got
a surprise for you.
You know a man
named Tony Angelo?
Yeah, he owns a
restaurant in Boston.
Well, he's flying some
fresh scrod out here for you.
Ooh, scrod? Eeuch.
Well, Tony oughtta know.
He served me enough of it.
(chuckles) Well,
with a little luck,
it'll be here for dinner.
Speaking of
Boston, Dr. Revere.
I'm not Russian!
Are you any relation to Paul?
- Paul Revere?
- And the Raiders?
No, I don't think so.
Oh, but I know Davy Jones.
Oh, doesn't matter.
Paul Revere wasn't much
of a ballplayer anyway.
Oh, (chuckles) I'm afraid
I'm as ignorant of sports
as I am languages.
And history and sociology and...
(MST3K theme music)
I think we should
stop for tonight.
Watching this guy
sleep is making me tired.
Look, I'm his
father and I can.
Oh.
The more patient
we are with him now,
the more cooperative
he'll be in the future.
Know what I mean?
Doctor, do you really think
that he believes he's home?
He believes he's at a Motel 6.
Well, I think he
has some doubts.
Well, I have some
doubts, too, Doctor.
Especially about the way
you're handling this.
You think you're the
only one who hurts?
All these questions
about his past.
These questions have helped me
to eliminate most
of his suspicions.
Most, but not all.
No, no.
It's only a matter of time now
before he figures what
we're doing to him.
But until then,
think of what we're learning
about their space program.
And, about dining in Boston!
(heart pounding)
I can hear my heart beating.
Let's dress 'im up.
He's so cute, I
hate to wake him.
My way is better.
(heart pounding)
You don't believe
that, do you, Doctor?
I believe you
can break him, yes.
Bend him, mold him.
There's always Ward E.
But you also stand a chance
of breaking his mind as well.
And a mind is a
terrible thing to waste.
And breaking up is hard to do.
And mulch is good for your lawn.
We will continue the
questioning another hour.
- Benedict.
- Arnold!
I can't devote my
whole life to this man.
This one man.
Oh, he wants to
play the field, huh?
More important things.
Yeah, he's got a
Botany 500 ad to do.
Doctor.
Another hour.
Okay, let me check that.
Scene three, I enter up left.
Attention all personnel.
Tonight's movie will
be Stranded in Space
starring Dorothy Lamour.
Neil, let's talk
about Paul Revere.
Well, the big
hook was costuming,
but after Cherokee
People, they really...
(machine beeping)
Drug's wearing off, Doctor.
Let 'im rest for tonight.
Give him another injection.
Too much o'that drug
is gonna kill 'im.
Then maybe we could
all get some rest.
This is a movie.
This is a movie on drugs.
Any questions?
That's for him!
(Tom humming a lullaby)
Ooh!
Benedict.
Get me security.
And some eggs, some
Hollandaise sauce,
a toasted English muffin.
(exclaiming, punch landing)
I think he's getting better.
(alarm blaring)
You have lovely skin.
Hi-kee-ba.
Gotta go! (chuckles)
(gun firing)
Oh, man!
I hope this hospital
treats gunshot wounds.
And no shoes!
Hey, where's he goin'?
Hey, he has to leave the
hospital in a wheelchair.
That's the law.
Oh, no hall pass.
I've had dreams like this.
I'm gun-shot and I'm
really late for class,
and I don't have a hall pass!
Oh, quick, in here.
Mr. Fisher's science room!
Switcher!
Let's go buff our helmets, Bob.
That was close. Too close.
That's it, I'll
dress as Murphy!
Oh, brother, Murphy's a woman!
But it's his size.
Who put the overalls
in Mrs. Murphy's locker?
Uh, uh, I wanna paint you.
Sort of.
Don't be afraid.
I won't hurt you.
I just wanna spread
you on some toast.
I won't tell
anyone you're here.
Help! He's in here! Help!
Yep, there she goes.
He's in there, in the lab.
I knew that.
Outta my way.
I want Rockford in my office!
Oh, excuse me.
He's turned into a
little light, sneaky.
Basement.
(synthetic chiming)
Come in.
I want Mannix.
This'll be great.
Watch this, Bob.
Steve, Al, you know what to do.
Oh, yes, sir.
We understand.
Benedict.
Fire.
(guns firing)
Now we make 'im talk.
(gasps) Oh, they shot
my spare turtlenecks.
I think Harry-O is behind this.
We gotta go.
We gotta get outta here.
Oh, no, they killed Snuggles!
I can't believe that.
(metal sliding and clanging)
No, no. I'm sorry.
- Oh, I'm afraid so.
- Oh, I'm afraid not.
- You're high.
- Oh, you're high.
I know you are, but what am I?
(mockingly) I know
you are, but what am I?
Hey, hey, come on.
What are you two little metal
monsters bickering about now?
It's all Crow's fault.
We were playing with our
Toppers TV tradin' cards
and I wanted to maybe trade
'im my complete Love Boat set,
which is worth a ton,
for his half-finished
Columbo villains,
and his crummy Name
O'the Game season two.
And now he tells me
my Love Boat collection
is incomplete
'cause I gotta have a card
for each time a star appeared,
and I say he's high.
Oh, who's high?
You know how much this Name
O'the Game pack is worth?
I'm talkin' James
Farentino, Tony Franciosa.
Big deal.
Hey, hold on.
Hold on now.
I think I can give us a little
insight into this problem.
Tom, you only want his
Columbo villains set
because you've got
Cameron Mitchell,
and his value just went up,
'cause he's in today's movie.
Oh, I guess so.
Yeah, and Crow,
you're not much better,
tryin' to scam Tom's complete
Loveboat season one set.
The set's not complete.
Oh, it is too.
Listen, I helped him
tape it together.
Look it, his arms
are inoperable.
I gotta do it.
See, all the cards go together
to form ship's
doctor, Bernie Kopell!
See?
Dick-weed.
Hey, knock it off
Hey, Crow!
Come on, what's wrong?
Well, I'm sorry.
I was just tryin' to play
hardball with ya, Servo.
Come on, no hard feelings, pal.
Okay. I guess not.
Okay, I tell ya what.
You can have the
whole Love Boat set,
and I'll forget about
the other stuff,
if you help me finish
my Sweathogs collection.
Well, you can have
Gabe Kaplan for free.
Oh, yuck, I don't
even want him.
I'm after Lawrence
Hilton-Jacobs.
Hey, well, listen.
I've got somethin' that'll
really make your mouths water.
The complete new
kids-in-court collection.
That's right.
Every major child star who's
been arrested, convicted,
or has litigation pending!
Check it out!
Wow.
Hey cool!
Hey, Servo, look, there's
stats on the back.
Charges, trial
status, even lawsuits!
Yeah, look, there's Adam
Rich from Eight is Enough!
Hey, the whole
Diff'rent Strokes gang!
Dana Plato for holdin' up a
video store with a pellet gun.
Allegedly, Crow.
That's right.
There's Gary Coleman
for suing his parents.
Hey, wait a minute!
Todd Bridges was acquitted!
That card's worthless.
Hey, I know, but listen.
I've got the complete set
now that I've got
Danny Bonaduce,
who was arrested for
beating up a transvestite.
Oh, wow, you got Bonaduce?
Hey, where'd you
get all this anyway?
Oh, I got 'em from Gypsy.
Gypsy?
She said all she had
were rabbi cards.
No, I just traded her
this Richard Basehart
from Voyage to the
Bottom of the Sea,
and she gave me
the complete set.
- (exclaiming) What?
- Oh, wow.
Gypsy, you come 'ere you rotten.
Tradin' is easy, once
you know the secret.
I'm Marshall Brodien.
(MST3K theme music)
Richard Basehart?
- I can't believe you, Gypsy.
- I got lucky.
Here's where switchin'
to Sprint'll pay off.
Yeah, no coin slot.
This is a better world!
Now what was
that number again?
(dial tone)
Number, please.
(Joel stammering)
A woman's secret
fantasy, please?
I wanna call Cape Kennedy.
Uh, the senator's
doing some offshore
drilling right now
Cape Kennedy,
General RE Williams.
I have no listing
for a Cape Kennedy.
You've got to.
It's a space center
outside of Orlando!
I have a Tony Orlando,
but that's the only one.
It's in Florida!
She was on Good Times.
Oh, you mean Esther Rolle?
Operator, you speak English.
There's got to be a Florida.
You're not dealing with AT&T.
If you care to speak
to my supervisor.
Your supervisor who?
Mr. Stalin?
Man, phone service
is so much better
where I come from.
(emulating Russian
accent) Nostrovia, comrade.
(all exclaiming)
Boy, that guy better
find a hospital.
He's wounded.
His pants fit good, though.
Very nice cut.
Haggars?
Fara.
For Guys, perhaps?
Dad 'n' Lad.
Sansabelt, I think.
Here's someone
who can help me.
Uh-oh, that's Jame Gumb.
(emulating Gumb) It puts
the lotion on its skin.
or else it gets the hose again.
Bye!
Been out there long?
Aw, few auditions,
Fruit of the Loom ad.
You know.
Oh, this your first
made-for-TV movie then?
Chinese lanterns?
So, where ya headed?
Well, I was
headed for Florida,
but I guess you ain't
got one o'those!
Those moons.
What about 'em?
Do they always look like that?
Sure, if you're hammered.
How do ya want 'em to look?
Well, they're supposed to
look like Jackie Gleason!
Third planet from the sun.
There's only one moon.
It's called Earth.
Did you ever hear of it?
Yeah, I'm not goin' that far.
Nope, never did.
Well, I'm writing a
short story about it.
Yeah, that's it.
Distant planet called Earth.
Oh, that was exciting.
Whoa, whoa, hang on a minute!
Something's wrong here.
Stryker. Neil Stryker.
He appears friendly.
- Snuggles, get off me.
- In point of fact,
he's unstable, paranoid,
extremely dangerous.
And he's cute when he
sleeps, but you know that.
A malignant disease
that must be eradicated.
With Eredicane?
Dri-Plan? Lasso?
Somethin' by Monsanto.
Roundup?
(mechanical shade whirring)
(chuckling) Hey, look!
They're in the Brady house!
Is there a question?
Yes.
He looks just like us.
I thought he'd be different.
Take my word for it.
Neil Stryker is different.
Stryker's a good cop!
How many of us are
to know the truth
about this man, Stryker,
that, uh, he's a stranger
from another planet?
Only those with
top-secret priority.
Inner council members
such as yourself.
For obvious reason,
there was no need to
alarm the entire planet
with the true facts of the case.
Oh, like Watergate.
Um, sir, how come
the Landers sisters
aren't at this meeting?
What facts will they be given?
They'll be told
to be on the lookout
for an escaped mental patient,
one considered
extremely dangerous.
Yet witty and urbane.
- Yes?
- Young Orson Welles?
Is he to be take alive?
He's to be taken.
That's all, thank you.
Now, I'll be in my
office on Tuesday,
but not Thursday.
Have your textbooks and
your syllabus with you.
Boy, you know how many
TV series'd be wiped out
if this room was blown up?
Let me tell ya.
Cameron, I just
wanted to say that
that speech was sterling.
I was moved.
Stop reading over my shoulder.
You? You got a problem?
Talk to my TA.
Yes?
He could be captured alive.
Mmm-huh.
Yes, Doctor, that's
a possibility.
You could order it.
Look out, here comes Jan!
Everybody scatter!
You don't understand,
do you, Doctor?
He's one man, alone.
One man alone.
Go shoot yourself.
Lemme tell you
something, Doctor.
Before the Perfect Order,
the history books were filled
with stories of one man alone
that changed the entire
course of our great planet.
One man alone wanting
to be dictator.
One man alone
thinking he was God.
One man alone feeling he knew
what was best for all mankind.
- Bush?
- Reagan?
Each of these men
caused suffering--
And a lotta bad theater.
Yes, that's true.
But this is different.
Different? How different?
He's given us proof
that intelligent life
exists elsewhere
in the universe.
Benedict, doesn't that
mean anything to you?
Think what we can
learn from this man.
I am thinking, Doctor.
Yeah, I thought I
smelled wood burning!
(all chuckling)
Our society works...
Because we all
believe the same way.
Just ask Werner Erhard.
We all feel alike.
We all dedicate ourselves
to what's best for
the Perfect Order.
And in turn, the Perfect
Order does what's best for us.
And then someone comes along
And doesn't pay union dues.
Someone with very
different ideas.
With very destructive ideas.
Do you know what I've learned
from this man, Doctor?
Oh, you're talkin' to me?
I've learned that he's cursed
with an absolute
freedom of thought.
He's cursed with an
inquisitive nature,
an uncontrollable spirit.
Oh, he's not
gonna sing, is he?
Much the same way most
of our planet was cursed,
before the Perfect Order.
Burger, fries, and a shake.
And now, Doctor, he's
walking freely in our streets.
In our midst.
Oh, believe me, Doctor.
Today, one man.
Tomorrow, 10.
In a week, a thousand.
Do you think I
look like Shatner?
In a month, an epidemic.
In two months, two epidemics.
Believe that?
No, but it was a nice speech.
Doctor, I'm asking
if you believe it.
I do, I do.
I do believe in spooks.
I do, I do, I do.
I.
Do you believe it?
Or. Not.
Yes.
Do you further believe he
must be dealt with quickly?
Once and for all?
Yes.
Do you believe
in little pixies?
Then we have no
quarrel, have we, Doctor?
No, but I'm gonna
whip your butt
in racquetball later.
No.
(smooching sound)
He needed that.
Alice, can you
make me a sandwich?
Great macrame.
You know, this
bookcase used to slide.
Henry, you think he was being
completely honest with me?
(chuckling) Nope.
Yes.
How quickly some forget.
How quickly.
Nice encyclopedias.
The suffering
Henry, suffering.
Did you ever see
anyone starve to death?
What'd you have in mind?
No, sir.
No, of course not.
You moron.
It's not a pretty sight.
Something you never will forget.
Jeez, I'm just a temp.
Henry...
Dr. Revere is lying to us.
He's taken Stryker's side,
which only proves how dangerous
a man like Stryker is.
I think Dr. Revere needs a rest.
What do you think, Henry?
Have him eliminated,
permanently.
- Ward E?
- Yes, I think, Ward E.
[Tom] Woody?
Woody?
(emulating Jame Gumb)
Now put the lotion
on your skin.
Boy, you know, I'm just crazy
about these split-level
Tudors around here.
They're great.
Really snappy.
Funny how space looks
- a lot like Sacramento.
- Yeah.
Or Ojai.
Smoke?
Hey, you saved the coupons?
Sure, how do you think
I got this swell truck?
Hey!
Hurt your hand?
What?
The only time I ever see
people use their right hands
is when they've hurt their left.
Oh, the unclean hand.
Use it all the time.
Sprained my wrist.
It's still a little sore.
Happened to me,
I'd starve to death.
It's exactly like our world,
except they're all left-handed!
Wow, I get it.
I know what you mean.
Takes some getting used to.
(music blaring from radio)
Ah, and so does that.
Ah, it's a left-handed radio
and a left-handed orchestra.
Heavy-handed.
Mmm-huh.
Radio Moscow here.
Boy, is that guy square.
With a capital square.
Hey, let's put somethin'
different on the tunage--
Senior Deputy of
the inner council.
To work for the Perfect Order
is to live in harmony
and peace with oneself.
To live in harmony and
peace is man's highest goal.
Page two?
To work for the Perfect Order
is to live in harmony
and peace with oneself.
Man, I hate it when
people sing along.
To live in harmony and peace
is man's highest goal.
Before our morning
wake-up exercises,
we have a special bulletin
from the Department
of Protection.
A mental patient--
(Crow dramatically coughing)
I'll get off right here.
Has escaped from
the medical center.
Well, this is as
far as I'm goin'.
I wanna thank you again
for stoppin' for me.
Not many people would've.
- Yeah, well.
- Thanks again!
Stryker may have been wounded.
Stryker is considered
extremely dangerous.
(MST3K theme music)
Oh, at least they've
got a Barnes & Noble.
(mockingly) Yes?
May I help you?
Uh, not without
hurting yourself.
I mean, what?
You looking for
something special?
Uh, yeah, I'm lookin'
for the new one,
American Psycho?
Do you have any
books about our planet?
About Terra?
- Yeah.
- Sure.
About where we are
in relation to the sun
and the other planets.
I'm afraid you'd have to go
to one of the technical
bookshops for that.
Perhaps some of those
near the university.
If you're interested in
the history of Terra,
I've got several
very good books here.
Let's see, over here,
Portnoy's Complaint.
This is most complete,
from the beginning, right
to the present time.
Oh, wait, isn't that
where Scarlett O'Hara lived?
You have any
with more pictures?
Yeah, and anything
not by Isaac Asimov?
So, it goes back
about 35 years?
That's right.
But you said,
from the beginning.
Yes, from the beginning
of the Perfect Order.
Oh, of course, Terra
had history before that.
You're too young
to remember that.
It had its bad times and good.
People seemed to laugh a
lot more in those days.
I was a woman then, too.
There seemed to
be music everywhere.
I remember the
concerts in the park.
Children pulled
apart like fresh bread.
Don't get me wrong.
Things are much better now.
The Perfect Order
has given us dignity.
There's no war
anymore, no starvation.
We all live together
in peace and harmony.
There's nothing prior
to the Perfect Order
worth recording or
even remembering.
'Cept the Beatles.
You're welcome to
browse around if you wish.
You won't find any obscene
reading material in this shop.
Then, why bother?
Got to try and make sense!
I thought that was a
book you couldn't put down.
Oh, can I do anything?
Got any Tama Janowitz?
No, I'll be all right.
I've a room upstairs
if you'd care to rest
for a little while.
No one would disturb you.
I'm quite alone here.
Really?
That's very kind.
Do you think you can make it?
Yes, thank you.
His name isn't Yoda,
by any chance, is it?
(oboe-based instrumental music)
Never mind the oboe.
That always follows
me around, you know.
It's small, but comfortable.
You can make yourself
some tea in there.
And there's fresh bread.
Or hooch.
Well, I think I'd just
like to rest a little while.
Well, whatever you want.
Uh, turn the Magic
Fingers on if you'd like.
Man, is this ever great!
I've got a place to live
and a brand-new dad!
Now I'll trash the room.
Well, maybe not.
Well, he'll be perfect
for my experiment.
You know, uh, that's
not a Tiffany lamp
It's a Debbie Gibson lamp.
- Oh!
- I'm kidding.
Oh, hello, Mother?
I've found myself
a new roommate.
Medical assistance, please.
Oh, great, a planet
full o'tattletales.
Where's Burt Convy?
District 1-1-4.
Yes, that's
right, the old man.
In the sweater.
Yes, I'll wait.
There's nothing else I can do.
Oh, that's exciting.
For cryin' out loud.
Last week, on McCloud.
I think the exercise worked.
Is that a diaper over there?
(door opening)
He's in there.
I saw you weren't feeling well.
I phoned medical assistance.
They've sent a doctor over.
Uh, you got a straight razor?
I wanna shave my wrists, yeah.
Oh, quick, give
myself a haircut.
Trim the sideburns.
Splash on some Canoe.
Oh, great.
Well, if it isn't little
Miss I-Won't-Tell-a-Soul.
(emulating
female) I trust you.
You've got to listen to me.
(Crow mumbles in muffled voice)
Bite my hand once for yes.
I'm an astronaut
from another planet.
- A planet called Earth.
- Yes, of course you are.
We were returning home
from a long mission and,
somehow, entered your
gravitational field,
and were brought down.
Mmm-huh. Go on.
When I came to, I
was at the hospital,
and the people there were
tryin' to convince me
I was back on Earth.
Now, you must've heard something
about an alien spacecraft
being recovered.
It's not something
that happens every day.
I heard that there was, uh,
a special patient in room 420.
That's him, get it?
And that Dr. Revere was
in charge of the case.
That's all?
If I'd needed to know
more, they would've told me.
'Cause they're perfect.
But I do know that Dr.
Revere is a very fine man.
He wouldn't do
anything to hurt you.
Dr. Revere kept me
drugged and a prisoner.
There, see, I told you
they were good people.
You must be mistaken.
Some patients do confuse
treatment with punishment.
The lucky ones.
So, you're telling me,
all he wants to do is help me.
Yes.
I'm not buyin' Trojans
with you dressed like that.
And quit followin' me!
Spread out. Come on,
we look conspicuous.
After all, you're
a very important man.
And when you've
completely recovered,
you'll be treated
as an honored guest.
With savage beatings.
A welcome visitor to Terra.
And I'm sure they'll be able
to help you get back to...
Earth, if you'll only
return to the hospital.
They won't hurt you.
I promise.
Ha!
All right.
On one condition.
We stop at the Dairy Queen.
That you drive me there.
I wanna turn myself
into Dr. Revere.
And I wanna turn
myself into Ivana Trump.
(foreboding music)
(all three vocalizing)
Yes, yes, it worked!
I'm gonna score on an
interplanetary scale!
TV movie.
Mission: Impossible music.
Hey, it's the Doublemint Twins!
What are they
shooting through, gauze?
That's right, you
can arrive on New Terra
in style in the new Plymouth
Fury, left-hand drive option.
You know, they shoot a lotta
Quincy scenes on this road.
And, up there, that's
where Columbo lived.
Um, I'd like to have
children right away
- if it's okay with you.
- Turn left.
Could we pull over first?
The hospital's the other way.
That's right.
You said you were gonna turn
yourself in to Dr. Revere.
- I lied. Turn.
- No.
I said, turn!
Like this!
(tires screeching)
Uh, that's nice, Mrs. Webb.
Uh, I think you're ready.
Uh, let's pull out into traffic.
Uh, Mrs. Webb?
Uh, that's, that's good.
Yee-hoo.
That was neat!
I gave you my word that
no one would hurt you.
You gave me your
word once before.
That was different.
I was lying.
Oh, sure.
I didn't know
who you were then.
That you're an astronaut
from a planet called Earth.
And that we're
traveling north on I-96.
Shhh. Now, quiet.
Grandma's watching her soaps.
You believe I'm an
escaped mental patient.
Hey, it's a made-for-TV
Charles Grodin up there.
You know, it would be so
nice if we weren't here.
And, um, over here is where
we film Dukes of Hazzard.
There's where Boss Hogg
got in his accident.
This road ends at Pine Ridge,
the autumn recreation park.
Pull up over there.
Now, pucker-up, Buttercup.
What are you going to do now?
I need some answers.
You're gonna give 'em to me.
Answers? About what?
We'll start with
the true and false.
About Terra.
If I'm gonna survive, I gotta
know what I'm up against.
Are there different countries?
Governments?
Is there any place I can go
where someone will help me?
Well, there's a
Fotomat up the road.
(outcries, honking horn)
Oh, great,
it's Norman Mailer
and Jack Henry Abbott!
Now they're dead for sure!
Hey, they're
gettin' some action.
Pull over, Earl. (chuckles)
Hey, uh, did Terra
just move for you?
You rude, impertinent,
wonderful man!
Can I call you?
Uh, so, does he
get to keep the car?
Like, what's she gonna do?
Tell a squirrel?
Maybe a woodchuck.
Oh, yeah, I never
thought o'that.
- Some kinda vermin.
- Yeah.
Perfect vermin.
I think this is
where the reunion is.
Hey, Funny Face.
Leave me alone.
Big Old Ruby Red Dress.
You're all I have.
Just tell me where
I can get some help.
Back at the hospital.
They tried to kill me there.
Oh, it wasn't personal.
You're mistaken.
Is this wound a mistake?
Are those men
chasing me a mistake?
Even if I am insane,
is this what the Perfect
Order does to insane people?
Burn!
No, the mentally
disturbed are treated,
and they're made well again.
They just have to
find your witch spot.
My own brother is.
What were you gonna say?
Uh-oh.
What? Nothing.
Nothing about my brother.
No, it was something
about you brother.
- No!
- What about it?
Nothing!
Is he mentally
disturbed, is that it?
(Tom vocalizing as if to
drown out Neil's words)
You don't know, do you?
They took him somewhere
for treatment,
and you don't know where he is.
Is that what happened?
Yes.
It was for his own good.
He kept writing things
against the Perfect Order.
He touched a nerve.
Telling people to revolt.
His name was Bukowski.
Is he still alive?
Uh, this is a hard question?
Let's just splendor
in the grass.
I need your help.
We gotta go.
I think for sure, this time.
- Really?
- Yeah, I think so.
- The radio!
- What?
The two-way radio!
I left it on in the
car so they'd find us!
(MST3K theme music)
Now, ladle in a heaping bag
full of delicious Nestle
Toll House morsels.
And then-
Hi, Crow.
Oh, man, I had a nightmare.
I dreamt Joel was takin' me
on a father-son fishing trip,
and Mom made us sandwiches
and stuff and cake,
and we had just finished
loading up the station wagon
with minnows and stuff,
when I noticed Joel
was wearing nothing
but a Christian Dior
bra and panty apron
and the really weird part was
he had a little
bellhop costume for me,
and then, the really
weird thing was, then,
I started screamin',
"No! Joel!
"I don't have the
legs for that!"
and he screamed,
"Oh, yes, you do."
And then, I said, "No, I don't.
"And stay away from me."
And he started chasin' me
around the station wagon.
And Mom came out
with a clown suit.
And then.
And then. I woke up.
What are ya doin'?
Oh, I'm making a
delicious taste-treat, Crow,
four-dozen fresh
Toll House cookies.
Mmmmm.
Let me help. Can I help?
I wanna help.
Okay, you can grease
those cookie sheets.
And don't use the
butter, it'll burn.
Hey, you know, Crow.
Your little fishing dream
reminds me of Ward
E from today's film.
Except, my vision of Ward E
is kinda like that
headache you get
when you eat something
really cold, really fast.
You know, like a Popsicle?
Oh, yeah, neat.
You know, but, I was thinkin'
what Ward E would be to me.
It's like comin' home
to find your answering machine
light flashing like mad,
only to find out the message is,
if you'd like to make a call,
please hang up and dial again.
Yes, that's good.
But, you know, to me,
Ward E is all about that
nauseating feeling you get
on the ride home from
church from a Sunday paper
that's been sitting
in the sun too long.
You know that inky stink smell?
But, no, no, no.
Ward E is that gross
feeling you get
when you push down the garbage
and somethin' wet and
unknown squirts on ya.
Eeew.
Right, fine, yes.
But how 'bout when
you're having a salad,
and that bacon bit
seems a little too hard
to be a bacon bit?
And, so, you take it out,
and it looks just a little
too much like a toenail.
(Crow groaning)
Rich, creamy.
Oh, Ward E is like sittin'
in a public bathroom,
and someone turns a light out.
Well, how 'bout when
you make a sandwich,
and you're this close
to taking a bite,
when you notice the bread's got
green fur all over the bottom.
(both groaning)
How 'bout when
you find yourself
absent-mindedly
fingering a wad of gum
on the bottom of
a theater chair?
Eww, hardened or wet?
(both groaning)
I can't believe you
guys started without me.
Whoa!
Ah! Ah!
Get 'im away from me!
Ah!
- What's wrong with him?
- I don't know.
Say, Joel?
Ever had to dig through the
hamper for a pair of underwear?
Oh, ish.
(exclaiming)
Oh, we got movie
sign already!
(metal sliding and clanging)
You asked for my help.
You saw what happened.
To get me, they'll
kill you, too.
Or, how 'bout in the morning,
and a booger's dripped
down the back o'your throat
and you (gagging sounds).
Don't ever wear that again.
(Tom chuckling)
I don't even know your name.
I'm T-H-X 1138.
Who are you?
That's pretty.
That's my mother's name.
Bettina.
Dr. Bettina Cook.
She's hot.
I've got two stars
next to her name here.
Check it out.
Citizen's profile
number D-R-7-3-2-4-1.
Oh, good thing they got
The Man from
U.N.C.L.E. computers.
Open channel B.
Whoa!
No, they're IBM.
(beeping)
Attention Kmart shoppers,
the blue light is flashing.
Oh, it's the Jan Brady phone.
Something important from Jan.
I'll get it.
He always calls
when we're at work.
Hello, Cameron, this is.
Hello, how are you?
I was just asking if.
Right away, sir.
You could pick up
some milk and some bread
on the way home from work.
No, sir, I won't be delayed.
Okay, then, make sure
you're home as soon as poss-
That was my mother.
We all have to answer
to someone, Henry.
Cops is filmed on
location in this guy's yard.
(oinking sounds)
Oscar, I brought another
infidel to see you.
Bettina.
Professor McCauley.
Huh, who's saying that?
I'm paranoid.
This is Neil Stryker.
He says he's an astronaut
from a planet called Earth.
(guffawing)
That's really great.
I'll get the sedative.
Do you believe him?
Yes.
In a kooky kinda way, yeah!
Well, you've convinced
this beautiful child
that anything at all exists
outside the Perfect Order,
you must be telling the truth.
Heh, put her there,
you big galoot.
But let's not discuss it here.
I have a feeling one
of these pigs is a spy.
(all three guffawing)
Oh, really, that
one right there.
Yet, some call him pig.
I think of butchering
him sometimes, but,
he might have friends
in the inner council.
(all three guffawing)
But, I kid the pigs.
Let's go on inside, huh?
(Crow humming)
Big room.
You're late, Number Two.
Do you have a two-minute
song prepared?
Be careful.
We just vacuumed.
Um, can I get you
a Coke, iced tea,
maybe some Country Time?
Benedict.
(Tom mimicing echoing sound)
Good to see you.
(all mimicing echoing sound)
My colleagues and I
have just been
reviewing your record.
You were very good in
The Crucible at Circle Rep.
Exemplary.
Thank you.
Oh, no, no, thank you.
No, thank you.
You've more than
justified my decision to
name you my successor when
I moved up to the tribunal.
I have only
followed the policies
you, yourself, established.
You're too modest, Benedict.
You've improved on them.
But...
There is a matter
that concerns us.
Your wardrobe.
The Stryker affair.
Oh, busted!
I assume full
responsibility for his escape.
I assure you, it's
only a matter of time
before he's recaptured.
By time you mean,
later this afternoon?
Perhaps this evening?
Or tomorrow morning?
Hopefully, sooner than that.
Around sixish some time today.
Then you have some
idea where he is?
Not exactly.
But, we do know he's in the
company of one Dr. Cook.
Dr. Bettina Cook.
Only one?
He may be forcing
her to help him.
Or perhaps she's helping
him without being forced.
Yes, we haven't
overlooked that possibility.
Say it, don't spray it.
In fact, I was
about to examine
her citizen's profile on
her when you sent for me.
I intend to find out
everything about the doctor.
You are one sick puppy.
I told you there was
nothing to worry about.
Er, tough crowd,
yeah, tough crowd.
Um, I thought it
was very funny, sir,
If that's any help.
I just love his meaty neck.
Mmm-huh!
The fact that he escaped
will go in your record.
A small mark.
But like a single spot
on a very white surface,
it tends to be
extremely noticeable.
(mockingly) He
sounds like Sylvester.
The longer this Stryker
is allowed to run free,
the more noticeable
that spot will become.
Does that mean you're
gonna stop spitting on us?
What was that?
- Oh, nothing.
- I understand.
I knew you would.
Eh, stick it, Baldie.
- What was that?
- Uh, nothing, sir.
I said I'd get 'em all.
Go away.
Oh, and, see my tailor.
He'll fix you up with
some nice, new clothes.
(all three exclaiming)
Same trees. Flowers.
It's like a dream.
A made-for-TV dream.
Perhaps, but for many years,
our scientists have
discussed the possibility
of a Terra twin.
As your scientists
must also have done.
That is, two planets,
flung out from the
sun at the same time.
Both of equal size and gravity,
and orbiting exactly opposite,
so that neither
ever sees the other.
Cooling simultaneously.
Oceans forming together.
And the first germs of life
appearing there, as here.
It's two, two,
two worlds in one.
Nothing exists by
chance in life, Neil.
Effect and cause,
cause and effect.
Precisely.
I think he's got it!
As life developed
here on Terra,
its counterpart
developed on its twin.
For every mountain
and valley here,
its counterpart developed there.
And so on through
the many long ages.
And so on, and
so on, and so on.
What did you call
your planet again?
Earth.
Dirt? Oh, Earth.
Has a very nice sound.
But I kid the other planets.
Kill him.
Now everybody
bring their suit?
We could skinny-dip. (chuckles)
Oh, this must be Terra's
Funniest Home Videos.
Oh, it's Out of This World
with Donna Pescow
and Doug McClure.
And, tonight on Star Search,
in the lab technician category.
Hey, it's the Miss
Alternate Universe pageant!
Uh, The Rick Dees
Show renewed again.
I don't get it.
Well, back where we started.
She has to turn up some place.
All of her friends are under
protective surveillance.
You mean the
friends we know about.
What about the ones we don't?
Like her poker buddies.
Oh, it's a possibility, Henry.
One we can't overlook.
I want that Rockford
matter taken care of.
Permanently.
So, you, uh,
heard about me?
We heard rumors that an
unidentified spacecraft
had been brought down,
and an astronaut taken
to the medical center.
Well, there were two
others on board with me.
We heard they were dead.
- And buried.
- In that order.
Where?
I don't know.
No services or prayers?
Or snacks?
Some of our older
people still pray.
But very softly, I'm afraid.
Kinda like nuns.
Religion has been outlawed
by the Perfect Order.
How did this Perfect
Order come about?
Oh, sarcasm.
Well, it seems we closed
our eyes for a little while,
and when we opened them again,
- Reagan was in office.
- It was here.
Can't you do
something about it?
What would you suggest?
Well, if enough
people oppose something!
How can puppets and--
- I resent that.
- Yeah, me too.
Men like yourself!
Toothless warriors.
Get dentures!
There's been a few
young men brave enough
to make their voices heard.
Young men who
disappear in the night.
All record of their births
and accomplishments destroyed.
Their families forbidden to
mention their names in public.
Like my uncle, oh,
oh, I did it again.
It's one thing
to have died, Neil.
Another never to have existed.
And then there's, uh, Ward E.
The Time Tunnel.
In color.
Oh, Ward E!
So, I hear they're filming
Get Smart on this set.
Hi.
Now then, you were
looking for something
in a deck shoe, I believe.
Ah, I like what you've
done with the place.
- Dr. Revere?
- I had Jell-O today.
Can you hear me?
You realize, of course, that
this is for your own good?
Lobotomy means never
having to say you're sorry.
Or anything else.
You were tired, Doctor.
You needed rest.
And that chair is
very restful, isn't it?
Now, Doctor, you can help me.
You do wanna help me,
don't you, Doctor?
Oh, I do.
That would please me to no end.
All you'll have to do is
tell me about Bettina Cook.
You were her professor
at the university.
She took advanced training
from you at the hospital.
We know that she
confided in you.
You know, of course, her
loyalty to the Perfect Order.
But, would Bettina
have any friends
that we don't know about?
I mean, if she thought that
we were looking for her,
is there some place
she could hide?
Well, she's got a tree fort.
Come on, Doctor.
You do understand me.
You're protecting her.
Why? Hmm?
Where is she?
Where is Betinna Cook?
Betinna Cook.
Betinna Cook, Doctor.
I heard ya the first time!
Oh, he's been like this
ever since he
started watching MTV.
That far?
I was told by your assistant
he was no further use to us.
What are we going
to do with you?
Uh, get me drunk?
Is it possible for me
to get back to Earth?
Anything's possible.
The fact that you got here in
the first place proves that.
Besides, Terra has a very
active space program.
Our crafts have great
range and capabilities.
- Are they ground controlled?
- To Major Tom?
Only during blast-off.
After that, the astronaut has
complete control of his ship.
Then all I have to
do is get aboard one.
Oh, (chuckles) you
make it sound like, uh,
catching a train.
There has to be a way, Dylan.
Thomas.
Hmm, maybe there is.
With my help.
Oh, I can't let you risk it.
But you can't
deprive an old man
of the one pleasure he
enjoys most in life.
Outwitting the Perfect Order.
Oh, I'm glad you said that.
Now, if you
could change places
with one of our astronauts.
Wouldn't it have to be
right before the launch?
That's when he has the
most people around him.
What about when
he's suiting up?
There's a guard
outside his room,
and a technician helping him.
All right.
That narrows it to two.
You'd only have about 30
minutes to make the switch.
That's all I need.
But even if you
got aboard, Neil,
could you handle the craft?
I'd sure give it a try.
You're cute.
It would help if I could
study some operations manuals.
I have all of them.
(moaning, glass breaking)
In my sternum!
The little black box.
Small table. Living room.
A bureau? Hutch?
Neil, Neil?
The television.
Oh, yeah, Pat Sajak
might see you, right?
This guy's a loon.
Yeah, he drinks, he takes drugs,
and he's gonna get
me off this planet.
Yep. Uh-huh.
Hmm, a little
candy for Grandpa.
Ooh, that's good smack!
Mmm-huh!
Mmm-huh.
(Joel shudders mockingly)
Ever, uh, speed-ball, Bill?
Come on, I wanna show you my
electric guitar collection.
I wasn't always a
toothless warrior, Neil.
I was a beat poet.
Hung around with Bill
Burroughs and the gang.
Another friend betrayed me,
and I was sent to Ward E.
I'm 19.
They couldn't afford
to tamper with my mind,
so they worked on my body.
I heard that gets pricey.
I have less than
a year to live.
I'm half Bondo.
Uh, Neil, I want
ya to promise me
you won't tell Bettina
what we're planning.
She's a lovely girl.
A good girl.
But so was the one
who betrayed me.
Both products of
the Perfect Order.
Now, let's go have
some naked lunch.
Are you all right now?
- Oh, yes.
- We have a lot to do.
There's a launch planned
for early tomorrow morning.
You know, he's a good friend.
A little messed up, but good.
- Neil Stryker.
- Denture wearer.
Astronaut, USA.
That's my home.
What, astronaut?
You smell great.
I'll never see you again.
Suppose you wanna
phone home now?
Neil.
Kneel?
Oh, my name, okay.
Oh, she's got four tongues!
She's a mutant!
Come on, do I have to
hose you off like dogs?
Get in here.
She makes love
just like a woman.
She takes love
But, she breaks just like
a little girl. (sobs)
Well said.
When I'm with her,
I'm in another world.
Spooky chick, huh, Doc?
Doc? Hey, Doc?
Well, now, this is a
visually-compelling
sci-fi flick, hmm?
They must've used the
same production designer
from Blade Runner, I'd say.
Yeah, the influence of
Fritz Lang's Metropolis
is apparent in every frame.
Oh, clearly evident.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah.
Stunning.
Well, they kinda remind me
of Terry Gilliam's Brazil.
There's a real kinda
surrealistic, visionary
Eraserhead quality.
- See the shrubbery?
- Dreamy.
(Bettina gasps)
This is not a
hotel, young lady.
Your mother and I
have been worried sick.
Um, I was, uh,
visiting my aunt.
Uh, yeah, my aunt.
And, uh, there was this thing
and I'm late because of it.
He just let me go.
I was going to call you.
Yes, of course you were.
We'll go somewhere else
where we can talk about it.
Uh, Steve, I want
you to kill her.
She's history.
Mmm-huh.
(all three mumbling)
Oh, tripped over you, there.
And now, back to Colossus:
The Forbin Project.
Fifty cents, please.
Professor?
Good afternoon.
I believe the director
left my new assistant's
name with you.
Dr. Allen Drake?
I'm sure it's on there.
The car, the windshield's
a little dirty.
What'd you say the name was?
Drake. Dr. Allen Drake.
Whatever I said the
first time, you know.
You should have it there.
Well, that's impossible.
I was with the director
when he told his secretary
to see that you got it.
Wanna take a look?
Oh, I'm not doubting
your eyesight.
Just the secretary's efficiency.
Here. His credentials.
Let's see, um, uh.
Uh, this is a pamphlet
on colon cancer, sir.
Oh, I, uh, put it
through the wash.
Chocolate bar was in a
shirt that I (mumbles).
You can't get anything
of first quality anymore.
Yeah.
Our security is, Pops.
I better check with
the security officer.
You do that.
Oh, and, while you
have 'im on the phone,
you better remind 'im
that if we don't make
our calculations,
there'll be no launching
tomorrow morning.
Ooh, that hurt, Gramps.
This is really strict security
for gettin' your film out
of a Fotomat, isn't it?
Pay the price.
Okay, three-by-fives.
Did you have any
duplicates or enlargements?
Dr. Drake.
Oh, good.
Now, thank you very much.
Thank you.
Grease him, grease him.
A lotta Chryslers
on that planet.
(MST3K theme music)
There's your
launching pad, Neil.
That's the bird that
will fly you home.
Looks like a rocket.
You see liquid
oxygen tanks like that
all over the base.
Juicy liquid oxygen.
They're filled from
a processing plant
out on the point.
All of our space complexes
are built by the ocean
in case a mission
has to be aborted.
Smart ocean.
Oh, and that's us
coming down the hill.
My wife shot this.
Three launch
buildings down below.
Seems a long way
from the launchpad.
There's an underground tunnel
that'll take you there.
It's only a
nickel, it's great.
And Neil?
- Yes?
- I love ya, son.
This all makes me feel
like a young man again.
I feel like a
young man, too, Bill.
Um, I'm Dr. Drake.
Huh?
No! No! No! (repeated)
Oh, who's that?
I don't know.
He's not all that scary.
Hey, does anybody know
where the launch fac, oh.
Now, the astronaut
will have his final
pre-flight examination
in this room.
That'll be at 0400 and
takes about 15 minutes.
And then comes the
critical 30 minutes,
because at 0445, he leaves
for the launching pad.
Right behind ya, sir.
With any luck, you'll
leave for the launching pad.
Now, the space helmet
will conceal your identity
until you reach the gantry,
and after that,
no one'll see you.
And what about the Tang?
I'm gonna go over
the pilot's checklist.
Oh, struck a Jack
Benny pose there
Once a junkie.
Is there another
vial somewhere?
No, just get a straw.
No, it's at home.
I'll have to get it, Neil.
Otherwise, I won't
be of any use to you
when you need me the most.
You go over that
checklist again.
I'll be back in time.
And there's milk
in the fridge.
And I made fudge,
but don't touch the
bars, they're for bridge!
Home is where the hypo is.
Note to myself.
Pack more life-saving liquid.
Go over to Korso's house.
Maybe he's got a string.
There's Jame Gumb again.
(emulating Gumb) I'm here to
put the lotion on his skin.
Just stop that now, okay?
I think it's cute.
(knocking)
Always somebody at the door
when I'm about to shoot up.
If it's not one thing,
it's another around here.
(knocking)
The Grandpa with
the golden arm.
Oh, no, oh.
They put 'er in a
room with Ike Turner.
Bettina?
What happened?
My name is Luka.
I live on the second floor.
Benedict was waiting for me.
Oh, no.
Eggs.
What'd you tell him?
Stop hitting me.
That Neil made me drive
him a long way from here.
And then let me go.
Did he believe you?
He threatened to, uh,
to take me to Ward E if I
didn't tell him the truth.
Instead, he took me to a,
a basement room somewhere.
Lech Walesa was
there, I don't know why.
He had two men there.
They.
Made me cook breakfast!
- They.
- He started juggling.
- I didn't tell them anything.
- He wasn't very good.
I didn't! I didn't!
There, there, I'll
make you feel better.
How 'bout a guest spot on
Tenspeed and Brown Shoe?
Professor?
Mary Ann?
I have to see Neil again.
I wanna be with him.
I wanna tell him I love him.
No, no.
Look at me.
I'm as helpless as
a kitten up a tree.
Don't I have the
right to see him again?
I'll make ya a nice
big punch, oh, sorry.
That's not enough.
I'm sorry, Bettina.
I got nowhere else to go!
Betinna!
What'd she want?
Bettina, you're covered
with light patina of bruises.
No, don't take the Plymouth!
It's a rental.
Gives me a headache, man.
Careful with the Plymouth!
I mean, the Starduster, I
mean, the TerraNova One.
Forget it, Joel.
Hi, Tim. Joe. Bob.
I hate Mondays.
Hi, clock.
Hi, bulletin board.
Hi, guy. Oh, it's him.
Dear Mom.
I hate Camp Grenada.
Time to put the
lotion on his skin.
Okay, who ordered
the passport to Earth?
I want to have a look at his
last telemetry measurements.
I'll get it from my files.
Will you set this
down for me, Dave?
Hey, thanks for including
my character name, Steve.
No, I'm not a letter!
It's, uh, good to
see you again, Eric.
It's been a long time.
Come on, I'll walk you outside.
All right, now, we've never
met before, have we?
You ever done magic before?
It's time for a little
trick we call metamorphosis.
My assistant, Eric, will, uh.
I promise, I won't
tell anyone you're here.
Not good enough for me.
Oh, I wasn't gonna
tell, but now I am.
You can bet it.
Just take your hands off me.
You're hurting my wrist!
It's okay.
He's perfectly fine, folks.
He's just under hypnosis.
I've seen this.
- Mmm-huh.
- Yeah.
It's an old one.
Uh, Neil, are you dumping me?
We gotta go, folks.
Right when it gets
good, I can't believe it.
(metal sliding and clanging)
So, once again, Mr. Rockford
has escaped our grasp.
Tibby and I are very
displeased, aren't we, Tibby?
Sorry, boss.
Next time, no mistakes.
I want him out of our way.
Permanently.
(laughing maniacally)
Right boss, ha ha!
Now, as for you.
Quincy's been nosing
around a little too much.
I think he's on to us.
I want that meddler
out of our way.
I'll see that he
takes a long vacation.
That means you're
gonna kill 'im, right?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Right. Okay.
(evil laughter)
Now, as for you.
I want Hooker dealt with.
Hooker's a good cop!
I know he's a good cop.
Had we been on the same team,
I think we might
have been friends.
He's a good cop,
but he'll make an
even better corpse.
(both laughing maniacally)
What was I supposed
to do, again?
Kill Hooker!
Oh, right!
Kill Hooker. Kill Hooker.
Now, Christie Love
has been sticking her
pert, pretty little nose
in our business long
enough and I want it out.
Our business?
Whaddaya mean by our business?
Well, uh, you know,
the things we do.
Like, illegal things,
and things that people
of a depraved nature do.
Well, why didn't
you just say that?
- For crying out loud.
- Well, it's implied!
Now, I want Christie Love
to take a deep, deep rest.
She needs her beauty rest, yes.
(both laughing maniacally)
Uh, 'scuse me, boss.
I'm a little confused.
I was supposed to permanently
eliminate Matt Houston,
and send Mrs. Columbo
on a long vacation,
so I flew to Houston,
and, are we supposed to
kill any of these people?
Yeah, that's the whole point.
You're supposed to
kill 'em all, I think.
Oh, right. Kill 'em all.
Okay.
Uh, say, boss?
Was I supposed to
have a long talk with
Petrocelli or was it
Banacek, the Polish guy?
And I didn't know whether to
take care of Toma or Baretta.
Uh, well, sir,
that's the same guy.
Oh, no, no, no.
Wasn't Toma Tony Musante?
Well, yeah, until they
moved the show out to LA,
and put Robert
Blake in the role.
- Oh.
- Epilogue in 10 seconds.
Well, you see, my little
friends, it works like this.
Epilogue in five,
four, three, two.
Epilogue now.
So you see, Rockford
is out of our way.
Quincy is on permanent vacation.
And Christie Love is
takin' a deep, deep sleep.
Well, my friends, it's
time to watch a film.
After this.
(all laughing maniacally)
Can't wear costumes
in the movie.
It's not allowed.
I love that sport coat.
Oh, my heart.
Oh, better turn bag (gags).
Uh, hey your lights.
Lights?
That little minx.
I'm getting a headache.
(Tom mimicking radio chatter)
Good.
Keep in contact.
Write if you get work.
You keep in touch.
(all three mumbling)
Next week on Medical Center.
I hate that.
Hey, it's Billy
Barty, all grown up.
Oh, hi, Bob.
Wait a minute, Bob's dead!
Have you seen Stoner?
No sir.
Well, that's strange.
Maybe he couldn't find
the telemetry record.
I may have a copy
in my office.
That's like him.
Good thing they talked loud.
Hmm, this looks like
a job for TV actor!
(Tom humming)
Are you decent?
I'm Dr. Drake.
There's gonna be a slight
delay in the launching.
Trouble with one of
the backup systems.
I have the new
countdown schedule.
Go away, I don't have a line.
Heh, works every time.
It's so '70s!
You've gotta teach me that.
Say, could I borrow your
hat for the Easter parade?
Goin' as a Jujube?
It happens we're both
in the same line o'work.
I don't get that.
Should I get that?
I don't know.
Seventies theme
show music. (repeated)
Oh, my heart.
Oh, better go back home.
Why can't I remember
to bring that stuff?
Professor McCauley!
Whoa, honey, you look
like five miles of bad road.
Yeah, People's Road '94.
I'd high-five, but uh.
I'm sorry.
I've got to see
Neil one more time.
Please, try to understand.
He's a magic man
(emulates rock song).
I understand.
I love 'im, too.
That's a good one.
Very funny, sir.
We'll be there
in a few minutes.
He won't get away.
Can you hold on
until then, honey?
I've got some
crackers in my purse.
Oh, shut up.
Henry?
Would it make any
difference to you if he did?
Well, yeah, shouldn't it?
I don't know.
Maybe.
If I fail,
they're gonna need somebody
else to take my place.
Uh, what size
shoes do you wear?
I'm not ready, Mr. Benedict.
Kill 'im.
(scoffs) You're ready.
I said that same thing once.
Me, too.
Well, you're right, Henry.
He won't get away.
Uh, take your hand
off my leg, sir.
Now I'll show you
how a real astronaut suits up.
(knock at door)
He's gonna put all
their clothes on?
(knocking) Neil? Dylan.
Thomas.
I brought the vag.
You have any trouble?
No, but she did.
No, it's okay.
Well, make it fast.
I'll keep watch.
Hi, dear.
How are ya doing?
Boy, you're oily!
Benedict was waiting for me.
He wanted to know
where you were.
Boy, they use a lotta
Plymouth Furies on this planet.
It's the planet of
the Furies, I think.
Go 'round the back.
Tell the doorman
you're with my team.
Goodbye, Neil.
Are you gonna be all right?
Don't worry about me.
The Perfect Order is kind.
(emulating President
Bush) Gentle.
Thousand points o'light.
Just.
Have you been hanging out
with Wendy O. Williams
and the Plasmatics?
Oh, hi, oops.
Neil? Neil!
(guns firing)
Hey, I wonder if he's
got any medicine for that.
Oh, I doubt it.
(guns firing)
(alarms blaring)
Uh-oh.
I just want my hair back.
(alarms blaring)
We're in Hooterville
all of a sudden.
(gun firing)
What are they
gonna do with 'im
once they catch him?
Make him dress like him.
Get the double-breasted
suit ready. (chuckles)
Next week on Mannix.
Last week on Cannon.
Coming soon on Hec Ramsey.
Previously on Baretta.
Tonight, a very special
episode of TJ Hooker.
This week on
Masterpiece Theatre.
Huh?
Oops.
(gun firing)
That one's for Florida!
(suspenseful music)
(gun firing)
That one's for not havin'
push buttons on your phones.
(gun firing)
(suspenseful music)
They got 'im.
They groupin' 'em.
Just fire into it.
(guns firing repeatedly)
Yeah, well here's
a left-handed one!
The most dramatic
confrontation
since Rommel met JC.
(gun firing)
- Heavy.
- Mmm-huh.
(MST3K theme music)
(Tom mimicking heavy breathing)
Wait a minute.
I got me an idea.
Wonderful, beautiful,
earthly idea.
Ah, this is just like
the end of Killdozer!
Cool!
(gun firing)
Hurts, don't it?
No, but that does.
That one's courtesy
of Paul Revere.
The real one!
Stop!
Don't shoot!
You'll blow us all up.
Get 'im.
Get 'im!
Are you all right?
Oh, sure.
Of course I'm not all right!
I took a slug in the arm.
I want him.
Boy, this is the biggest
basement I've ever seen.
What, are they in
Aaron Spelling's house?
(sirens in distance)
Goes on forever.
(sirens wailing)
The Rat Patrol.
In color.
(suspenseful music)
(Tom mocking music)
Oh, man.
Clowns to left of me,
jokers to my right.
Here I am, stuck in
a made-for-TV-movie,
with you.
(Tom mocking music)
All right, friend.
Prepare to meet Kali.
In hell. (chuckles)
What's he gonna do?
I mean, there's
really no way out.
No, this is the end for him.
Yeah, pretty much just,
they take him and he surrenders.
(humming)
Lotta sexual tension, though.
Yeah, I'll give you that.
(humming)
It looks like Acapulco
over here by the cliff.
(humming)
Oh!
Next week on MacGyver.
Krakatoa, east of Java.
Check it out.
Out of focus.
(alarms blaring)
Oh, hi, Rick.
Looks like he just heard
from Dean Witter. (chuckles)
Wardrobe!
Nothin' up my sleeve.
Again?
Get out of my way.
The closer he gets.
The better she looks.
Well, maybe not.
(emulating Bettina)
Are you still mad?
You did the right
thing, Bettina.
Thanks to the Perfect Order,
we have one great
family here on Terra.
A dysfunctional family, but.
Destined to
protect each other.
Destined to help each other.
Destined to look
after each other.
Destined to be trapped
in made-for-TV movies.
My brother lives in Florida.
Gum?
He couldn't have
survived the explosion.
I want proof of this.
I want proof.
Proof?
His charred
bones, if necessary.
Mmm, charred bones, mmm.
One of the men found this.
Stryker must've lost it on his
way to the chemical building.
Didn't think it'd fit
in my pants, did ya?
Can't see.
Oh, he dropped the thing
that's gonna drive
the whole series.
Drop in any mailbox,
postage guaranteed.
(mimicking Bettina) I
had forgotten his name
after the lobotomy.
Kinda ran her pantyhose
there, didn't she?
Yeah, it's been a
crappy day for her.
Lemme tell ya.
Calgon, take her away.
(Joel sputtering)
Water.
The source of all bad acting.
And how.
And so, standing erect,
he emerged from the slime.
(groaning) This looks
like a good place.
He's his own From
Here to Eternity.
Oh, now, what is it?
What happened?
(coughing) From other planet.
Thing crashed.
Had girlfriend.
Blew stuff up.
Capsized.
I had to swim to shore.
Ah, made for TV, huh?
Joe, get me my coat.
But not the good one!
We've been, uh,
we've been campin'
here a couple days.
We're gettin' ready to
leave in a little while.
Which way you goin'?
Uh, up the coast.
So are we.
Yeah, toward Stephen
Cannell's house.
You're welcome to ride
with us if you want.
But sit on a towel.
Thanks.
Here, friend.
Nice.
My name's Mitchell.
Cameron.
James Mitchell.
Yeah, right.
And my name's Peter Rabbit.
Tom Nelson.
Mike Nelson.
Come along.
Does that guy
realize he's gonna get
a lobotomy just for
fraternizing with that guy?
Oh, what the heck.
So long, Chinese lanterns.
Is it possible for me
to get back to Earth?
Anything's possible.
The fact that you got here in
the first place proves that.
What?
That doesn't sound the same.
It's our old friend Karl
Demer again, isn't it?
It's the big
pretzel in space.
Hey, they're getting
better with these holy-grams.
They changed that
one back and forth.
Music by Kraftwerk.
It sounds more like
Super Mario music to me.
You know,
this movie was originally
titled The Stranger,
but, you know, I didn't see
anybody dying on the beach.
It doesn't look anything
like Camus to me.
I don't understand.
Fun, fun, fun in the autobahn.
Autobahn, autobahn,
pa-tom-pom-pom.
Can we get outta
here now, please?
Another day,
another food tablet.
(metal sliding and clanging)
Looking forward to
lunch at The Polo.
Yours truly, Tommy Servo,
executive in charge
of production,
Satellite of Love Studios,
et cetera, et cetera.
Hey, read that
back to me, honey,
will ya, Magic Voice, baby?
Dear Mr. Ovitz.
You just don't know how to
take no for an answer, do you?
Uh, Mr. Servo.
There's a Joel Robinson
and a Crow here to see you.
Oh, send 'em in.
We'll go over that letter lady.
Okay, whadda you two
pixies got for me?
It better be hot,
better be good.
Uh, did you see
the movie, sir?
Did you see Stranded in Space?
Yeah.
Yeah, what'd you think?
Dynamite, huh?
And what a series it'll make.
A series?
Oh, come on.
Look, kid, I was thinkin'
it was an okay pilot,
but I just don't see
it as a series, please.
Are you kidding?
It's got all the ingredients!
It's The Fugitive
meets Logan's Run
with Please Don't Eat
the Daisies sprinkled in.
It can't miss!
Oh, come on.
Look, look, if Stranded in Space
becomes a series,
that lead has got to go.
I was thinkin' of
maybe David Janssen.
Yeah.
But, uh, David Janssen's dead.
Oh, and that actor
there was alive?
Gimme a break, come on.
'Scuse me, Mr. Servo.
the Maitre D' at
Spago just called,
and I'm sorry, there are no
tables available tonight.
Oh, heck.
I guess I'll just have to
use the drive-through, then.
Okay.
David Geffen on line three.
Geffen?
Oh, I'm gonna take that call.
Hey, look, Joel, press that
button for me, will ya?
My arms are inoperative, babe.
Thank you.
Say, Geffen.
Hey, look, I'm very upset.
Listen, I'm very upset.
You assure me that Kevin
Costner and Julia Roberts
are all set to sign.
Now you tell me they
been replaced by
Bill Bixby and Joanne Whalley?
I'm gonna plotz right
here, you listen to me?
I consider it as a
personal betrayal.
I'm gonna bury you man.
Do you hear me?
Bury you.
Get outta my face.
Um, you know, Mr. Servo,
I think we should
read this letter.
Yeah, why not?
Sure.
Dear MST3K.
My husband is a big
fan of this program.
He is 52 years old,
and he's an aircraft mechanic.
He never misses it.
His name is Bob.
It's from Dee Moore.
Oh, that's beautiful.
I love it.
I can see Gil Gerard as
Bob, the aircraft mechanic.
Lindsay Wagner as Dee,
his long-suffering wife.
Oh, boy, it's beautiful.
It's got legs, it's got heat.
It's got everything.
Sign 'em up!
What did you think, sirs?
Ah, show business
and mad science.
Two very fickle, very
unstable professions.
You know, Frank, I may be forced
out of my position one day,
and a replacement
will have to be found.
Really?
Yes.
An assistant, perhaps.
Someone next in line.
Well, what?
We put an ad in the paper,
or something like that?
Frank, you just don't get it.
In all likelihood,
it would be someone from right
here at Gizmonic Institute.
Someone who's worked
very closely with me.
(scoffing) And then I
have to train 'im in, right?
Oh, Frank, Frank.
I offer you the world and all
you see is middle management.
Push the button.
Hey, is this suit
coming outta my salary?
(sighing)
("Mighty Science Theater")